{
    "quiz": [
        {
            "id": 1,
            "theme": "Vinter Quiz",
            "icon": "‚òÉÔ∏è",
            "questions": {
                "question1": {
                    "question": "Hva slags farge har absint?",
                    "alternativeA": "Gul",
                    "alternativeB": "Bl√•",
                    "alternativeC": "Brun",
                    "alternativeD": "Gr√∏nn", 
                    "answer": 4
                },
                "question2": {
                    "question": "P√• et tastatur, hvilken bokstav er mellom Q og E?",
                    "alternativeA": "A",
                    "alternativeB": "W",
                    "alternativeC": "S",
                    "alternativeD": "D",
                    "answer": 2
                },
                "question3": {
                    "question": "Hvem oppfant den elektriske lysp√¶ren?",
                    "alternativeA": "Thomas Edison",
                    "alternativeB": "Humphry Davy",
                    "alternativeC": "Isaac Newton",
                    "alternativeD": "Charles Darwin",
                    "answer": 1
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "theme": "P√•ske Quiz",
            "icon": "üê£",
            "questions": {
                "question1": {
                    "question": "Hva slags farge har absint?",
                    "alternativeA": "Gul",
                    "alternativeB": "Bl√•",
                    "alternativeC": "Brun",
                    "alternativeD": "Gr√∏nn", 
                    "answer": 4
                },
                "question2": {
                    "question": "P√• et tastatur, hvilken bokstav er mellom Q og E?",
                    "alternativeA": "A",
                    "alternativeB": "W",
                    "alternativeC": "S",
                    "alternativeD": "D",
                    "answer": 2
                },
                "question3": {
                    "question": "Hvem oppfant den elektriske lysp√¶ren?",
                    "alternativeA": "Thomas Edison",
                    "alternativeB": "Humphry Davy",
                    "alternativeC": "Isaac Newton",
                    "alternativeD": "Charles Darwin",
                    "answer": 1
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "theme": "Sommer Quiz",
            "icon": "üèñÔ∏è",
            "questions": {
                "question1": {
                    "question": "Hva slags farge har absint?",
                    "alternativeA": "Gul",
                    "alternativeB": "Bl√•",
                    "alternativeC": "Brun",
                    "alternativeD": "Gr√∏nn", 
                    "answer": 4
                },
                "question2": {
                    "question": "P√• et tastatur, hvilken bokstav er mellom Q og E?",
                    "alternativeA": "A",
                    "alternativeB": "W",
                    "alternativeC": "S",
                    "alternativeD": "D",
                    "answer": 2
                },
                "question3": {
                    "question": "Hvem oppfant den elektriske lysp√¶ren?",
                    "alternativeA": "Thomas Edison",
                    "alternativeB": "Humphry Davy",
                    "alternativeC": "Isaac Newton",
                    "alternativeD": "Charles Darwin",
                    "answer": 1
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "theme": "H√∏st Quiz",
            "icon": "üçÅ",
            "questions": {
                "question1": {
                    "question": "Hva slags farge har absint?",
                    "alternativeA": "Gul",
                    "alternativeB": "Bl√•",
                    "alternativeC": "Brun",
                    "alternativeD": "Gr√∏nn", 
                    "answer": 4
                },
                "question2": {
                    "question": "P√• et tastatur, hvilken bokstav er mellom Q og E?",
                    "alternativeA": "A",
                    "alternativeB": "W",
                    "alternativeC": "S",
                    "alternativeD": "D",
                    "answer": 2
                },
                "question3": {
                    "question": "Hvem oppfant den elektriske lysp√¶ren?",
                    "alternativeA": "Thomas Edison",
                    "alternativeB": "Humphry Davy",
                    "alternativeC": "Isaac Newton",
                    "alternativeD": "Charles Darwin",
                    "answer": 1
                }
            }
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "theme": "Jule Quiz",
            "icon": "üéÑ",
            "questions": {
                "question1": {
                    "question": "Hva slags farge har absint?",
                    "alternativeA": "Gul",
                    "alternativeB": "Bl√•",
                    "alternativeC": "Brun",
                    "alternativeD": "Gr√∏nn", 
                    "answer": 4
                },
                "question2": {
                    "question": "P√• et tastatur, hvilken bokstav er mellom Q og E?",
                    "alternativeA": "A",
                    "alternativeB": "W",
                    "alternativeC": "S",
                    "alternativeD": "D",
                    "answer": 2
                },
                "question3": {
                    "question": "Hvem oppfant den elektriske lysp√¶ren?",
                    "alternativeA": "Thomas Edison",
                    "alternativeB": "Humphry Davy",
                    "alternativeC": "Isaac Newton",
                    "alternativeD": "Charles Darwin",
                    "answer": 1
                }
            }
        }
    ]
}
